We finally found them!
This is Star Platinum!
Jolyne Cujoh.
Did she defeat the guard
by herself and take the discs?
I will return the disc to my father.
Along with the disc held by Pale Snake…
No matter what.
Of course.
All memories relating to myself
have been deleted from Miraschon's disc.
Therefore, no one
will be able to track it to me.
The difference between humans and animals,
is that humans seek heaven.
Humans ought to lead a life
that leads them to heaven.
This is what makes humans beautiful.
EPISODE 10: OPERATION SAVAGE GUARDIAN
(HEAD TO THE COURTYARD!), PART 1
-Soap.
-Here's my rent.
I want the most expensive watch you got.
Move.
I'm using the phone next.
What?
Are you crazy, bitch?
I'll take real good care of--
Take a seat! You won't get tired!
Here's a complimentary drink.
Feel free to ask me again.
This is The Speedwagon Foundation HQ
in Dallas, Texas.
We do not accept
collect calls on this number.
I looked up the number in a phonebook.
I only have this number.
And I'm an inmate
at the Green Dolphin Street
State Prison in Florida.
My name is Jolyne Cujoh.
Please connect me to someone
who knows what this means.
Please hold.
Thank you for waiting.
Are you Professor Jotaro Kujo's daughter?
And you are?
I am just a foundation representative.
And I am not a Stand User.
I see.
But you seem to know
about Stand abilities.
Do you know about the discs?
Yes, of course.
After retrieving
Dr. Jotaro Kujo's body from the UUV,
he has been sheltered, not here in Dallas,
but somewhere safe.
I am so sorry to inform you of this,
but your father is medically unresponsive.
If I say that we can bring him
back to life, will you believe me?
I am merely a scientist. I cannot comment.
I have obtained a disc.
Just one of them.
We can bring him back.
I just know that
the discs will bring him back.
I'll do whatever it takes
to deliver them to you.
I just don't know how to do it.
I want you to come up
with a plan to deliver the discs there.
Immediately.
Isn't this conversation
being recorded by the prison?
Yes, probably.
But that's a risk I'm willing to take.
I have no time.
This is urgent.
I'm in a dangerous situation
where I cannot hide the disc anywhere.
There must be a way.
And just so you know,
I am not allowed visitors.
I understand.
Since you insist…
What about the courtyard?
The courtyard?
Do you mean the courtyard
between the men's and women's prisons?
Yes.
Please be there in 20 minutes.
I can manage something.
In 20 minutes?
From now?
Yes. You said this is urgent.
If you instruct us to retrieve the discs,
we will do everything we can to do so.
If you say he will be revived,
we believe you.
However,
we are a non-militaristic
medical research foundation.
We neither have the resources
nor the ability to help you escape
or save your life.
Is that risk acceptable to you?
Okay. I'll be there.
And how will you retrieve the disc?
We shouldn't speak of that over the phone.
But please look for Savage Guardian.
You will understand then.
Let's call it
Operation Savage Guardian for now.
Savage Guardian…
Is that an object?
Or is it a person?
Fine.
I need to head to the courtyard.
I'm at the cafeteria
of the women's prison.
To get to the courtyard,
first, I must pass through the gate,
go up the stairs in the back,
cross the second floor corridor
to get to the medical wing
from the women's prison.
You may pass.
FE40536, you're the nuisance
who got sent to the Punishment Ward.
Your access to different parts
of the facility is restricted.
Jolyne.
Emporio!
Here! Do not touch the ball.
We can't let others see us.
Come with me.
Wha…
Emporio, those two…
It's fine, they can be trusted.
He prefers to sleep on a bed,
but this room doesn't have one.
So he ends up sleeping in the piano.
Jolyne, I live in secret
in this ghost of a room.
Ghost of a room?
Does that mean you're…
No, Jolyne.
He and I are alive.
We aren't ghosts.
You can touch us.
We're warm and have pulses.
Listen closely.
Ghosts do not live here,
but the building itself is a ghost.
What?
Does "the ghost of objects" make sense?
This prison caught fire in 1984
and went through a huge renovation.
This room burned down in that fire.
This room belongs in the past.
It's a ghost of the music room.
So… this means… Emporio,
are you…
Ever since I was born,
I've been able to materialize
the ghosts of objects.
That's my Stand ability.
But I can only use them.
So even this chocolate bar
and this orange juice…
I can't consume them.
But they still have a taste.
They're quite good.
What?
Don't worry.
This clock stopped
when it burned along with the room.
You still have time
before your 20 minutes are up.
But…
you made a plan to deliver the disc
over the phone.
How reckless!
I understand your situation.
Pale Snake will learn about this.
Please, Emporio.
Tell me how I can reach the courtyard.
Don't misunderstand me.
I can't access just any place
from this ghost room.
I use the ghost items like this
to get around without getting caught.
I know you have no choice.
He says he wants to tag along.
You should take him.
He can aid your cause.
His name is Weather Forecast.
This is a music room.
Don't be so alarmed.
Weather doesn't talk much
because he has no memory.
-Memory?
-Yes.
He has no memory of his childhood
or when he arrived here.
He's serving a six-year sentence.
He has a habit of walking on tip-toes.
He's a TV guide fanatic,
but he doesn't watch TV.
When he talks, he barely opens his mouth.
And he talks right up to your face,
so you may feel his lukewarm breath.
He has no memory?
Is that because
Pale Snake stole them from him?
Probably.
He wants to learn about himself.
He also wants to know
why Pale Snake wants your father's discs.
He says his Stand ability
is not tied to the discs.
He was born a Stand User.
As for his ability…
he can manipulate the weather to his will.
His Stand name is…
Weather Forecast.
Pretend you didn't notice him.
Someone was peeking to see
where the music was coming from.
Now it's confirmed.
Someone knows you made a move
and came to check on you.
And we now know his face.
STAND NAME: JUMPIN' JACK SPARK
STAND MASTER: LANG RANGLER
Dammit. He's already close.
But if he's a Stand User,
we need to take care of him now!
No, Jolyne.
We should hide for now.
He doesn't know that
you're headed for the courtyard.
He didn't hear your phone call
and that's why came to eavesdrop!
If he knew, he would have
waited at the courtyard.
That's why, right now,
he's chasing us!
What's up with him?
Turn into that corner
before he gets any closer. Hurry!
Just as I thought.
He doesn't know
where you're going yet.
But what's with him?
He had a weird way of running.
We were able to hide because he's slow.
Anyway, you need to head to the courtyard.
Your phone call earlier
was definitely recorded,
but I don't think Pale Snake heard it yet.
The sooner you go,
the less dangerous it'll be.
The medical wing is up ahead.
Once you go downstairs
and pass the medical wing,
there's a gate for the corridor.
It leads to the factory.
It also leads to the men's prison
across the courtyard.
The medical wing is accessed
by both men and women.
Weather Forecast is a man,
so if tells a guard
he's going back to the men's prison,
he'll have no problem
getting to the connecting corridor
and getting to the factory entrance.
Go on ahead.
I need to bribe the guards, right?
Is 50 dollars enough?
Tell them you want your boots repaired
at the factory.
But even if you manage
to pass the medical wing,
you'll have to get to
the courtyard by force.
The security is light,
but if you get caught, they'll shoot.
and you'll get five more years
for trying to escape.
By force, huh?
Guess I have to get used to using it.
I just have to go.
Another five years
is nothing at this point.
Thank you, Emporio.
Right.
This is the most I can do.
Please revive him.
If your father comes back to life,
then I think
I might be able see some hope.
Oh, dammit.
What's wrong with this cola?
You touched the can, didn't you?
Did you shake the can?
Get me another one, will you?
Oh, I didn't touch it.
I only touched the plate.
My shoe's got a hole on it.
Over in the back. Can you see it?
I wanted to get it repaired
at the factory.
Oh, man, my cola spilled.
Where did I put that washrag?
"Go get a cola"?
You really want me to get one?
And you want me to pour it into this cup?
Do that yourself why don't you…
What's going on?
Oh, here's the washrag.
You can go. But make sure
to be back here in 20 minutes…
Oh, she already left.
What? Where's my cup and the plate?
What's happening?
Could it be…
This is…
The plate is floating!
The cup and the boot as well.
But, the contents of the cup
aren't spilling out.
It turns into balls of liquid and floats!
Everything I touch is floating upwards!
That money must have floated out
of that guard's pocket!
I'm in the air too.
Since when that strange guy
started chasing me...?
He spit at me then.
Did that cause this?
The disc!
Dammit. It slipped out when I rotated!
Stone Ocean!
My thread! I can't control it!
There is no up and down.
There's no gravity!
I'm in zero gravity!
You're going back to the men's prison?
Okay. Go ahead.
This is bad! He'll take my disc!
If I try to punch, I'll lose my balance.
I need to focus.
Aim in a single direction like a rocket!
What?
Dammit. I can't destroy this disc.
It just comes back like rubber.
That's why Pale Snake
told me to just collect it.
Hold on!
Weather Forecast,
don't go any further!
Can you hear me? I'm being attacked!
He took my disc.
If we lose him now, everything is over.
Everything will end!
Don't let him go!
No…
My voice can't reach him.
What a nuisance.
Jolyne Cujoh,
I thought I only needed to kill you.
Jumpin' Jack Spark!
Weather Forecast,
his ability takes away gravity.
Do not touch whatever it is he projects.
You'll become weightless!
Zero gravity.
So you are a Stand User yourself.
Surely, you understand
the implications of my ability.
He projected
pieces of junk.
Weather Forecast.
This man, who is said to
control the weather,
is a mystery to me.
But that cloud-like thing
must be a layer of air.
He used its resistance
to deflect the enemy's attack.
And he's using
centrifugal force to spin his arm.
It's weightless,
it can accelerate forever
with that spinning force.
His body's center of gravity won't change,
so he can accurately project
a powerful attack.
Jumpin' Jack Spark!
Weather Forecast!
This flame!
Aerodynamic friction?
Dammit, it's spreading!
Zero gravity, deactivate!
Meet your end!
Corridor 7B.
Emergency alarm activated.
Dammit. That impact…
And I have the disc, too!
The gate is closing.
What do I do?
It's even harder
to get to the courtyard now.
But I have no choice.
The enemy will be trapped too!
This is my chance to get back the disc!
What the hell?!
Everything you touch…
becomes weightless… Right?
Jolyne Cujoh?
The courtyard is just ahead.
But where did he go?
I need to get the disc back!
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter